Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Activities, 1919-1990; MS2142 Series 3; 15 Linear feet (Box 70, Box 71, Box 68, Box 69, Box 55, Box 67, Box 52, Box 53, Box 43, Box 42, Box 54, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 51, Box 50, Box 49, Box 48, Box 47, Box 46, Box 45, Box 44, Box 65, Box 66, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64)
  - Activities, undated (Box 56)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "M" names, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "M" names, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "M" names, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "M" names, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "M" names, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "M" names, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "N" names, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "N" names, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "P" names, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "S" names, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "S" names, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "Y" names, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - Consultation cases, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - Non-opened cases, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - Short term counselling, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Work - statistics, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Work - reports, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Activities, undated (Box 57)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files A-B, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files C-D, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files E,F,G,H -, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files I-J, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files K-L, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files M-N, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files O-P, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files R-S, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files T, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Financial Assistance Case Files V-W, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Work Job Description, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Essay on psychoanalysis by case worker, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Narrative reports, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Social Work, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Obituary - Mary Moore Miller, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Social worker at Friendship House in 1930-1940
  - Activities, undated (Box 58)
  - Education - narrative report, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Education - monthly reports, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Education, 1970 ca. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Educational proposal for Friendship House, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - .Special Events: List of Christmas events, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Special Events: "Race Relations Sunday", 1945 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Special Events: Tea at Friendship House, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Special Events: Several special events, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Special Events: Visit of First Lady of Upper Volta, 1960 ca. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Special Events: Tea, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Special Events: Folk Fest, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Special Events: Ted Mack Benefit Show, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Special Events: Celebration luncheon, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Special Events: Folk Fest (Congressional Circle event), 1962 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Special Events: Halloween party, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Special Events: Open House, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Special Events: White House Christmas party, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Special Events: Cookbook for children, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Special Events: Retirement party, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Special Events: Visit of First Lady of Malagasay Republic, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Special Events: Lady Bird Johnson's visit, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Special Events: Lady Bird Johnson's visit, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Special Events: Distinguished visitor, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Special Events: Lady Bird Johnson dedicated play ground, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Special Events: Japanese cabinet wives visit 196., undated (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Special Events: Mayor Walter Washington's visit, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Special Events: Benefit, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Special Events: Visit from a clown, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Special Events: Lecture and concert series, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Special Events: Congressman Dellum's lecture, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Special Events: Rosalyn Carter's visit, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Special Events: R, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Activities, undated (Box 59)
  - Credit Union: Charter, beginnings, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Credit Union: Memo of Understanding, contract, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Credit Union: Newsletter, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Credit Union: Statistics, finances, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Credit Union: Meetings, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Credit Union: General, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Credit Union: Memo of Understanding, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Credit Union: Policies, etc., 1966 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Credit Union: Statistics, finances, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Credit Union: Meetings, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Credit Union: Newsletter, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Credit Union: Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Credit Union: Annual Report, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Credit Union: Typical cases served, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Credit Union: Budget, 1966-1976 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Credit Union: General, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Credit Union: Finances, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Credit Union: Statistics, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Credit Union: Meetings, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Activities, undated (Box 60)
  - Credit Union - general, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Credit Union - financial, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Credit Union - reports, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Credit Union - Annual reports, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Credit Union - meetings, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Credit Union - general, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Capper Consumer's Federation, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Credit Union - fiances, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Credit Union - meetings, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Consumer Action Program, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Credit Union - general, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Consumer Action, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Consumer Action, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Credit Union, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Credit Union, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Credit Union, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Consumer's Co-op Store, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Consumer's representative Ron Cooper, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Summer Programs - list and schedule, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Summer Programs, Summer School, 1950-1953 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Summer School class, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Summer Program, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Summer Program - outline of program, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Summer Service Corps, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Summer Programs, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Summer Enrichment, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Street Camp (Summer Enrichment) 196., undated (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Summer Programs, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Summer Enrichment, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Winter Programs, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Summer Programs - funding requests, teen clubs, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Summer Programs, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Winter Enrichment, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Summer Programs in the Arts, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Summer Activities, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Summer Activities, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Summer Activities, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Activities, undated (Box 61)
  - Public Health - Health Posters, 1950 ca. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Poverty program announced (Neighborhood Development Program of the United Planning Organization), 1960 ca. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Public welfare crisis, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Pre-release guidance center - halfway house, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Guidance Center - Halfway House, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Citizen's Committee on the Public Welfare Crisis, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Halfway House - Guidance Center, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Anti-poverty program at Friendship house, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - "Community Laundries", 1965 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Friendship House programs, Wall Street Journal, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Welfare - Public Welfare Crisis, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Testimony to Senate Committee on Welfare, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Community Laundries, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - UPO War on Poverty - funds cut, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Community Laundries, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Clothing Center - food and clothes distribution, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - "Poverty Workers School" at Friendship House, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Comments on Beautification Program vs. other aid, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Buying Club, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Community Laundries, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Community Laundries, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Gas Station (an anti-poverty program), 1970 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Food Stamps, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Report on Hunger, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Clothing Center - sample forms of donations, corresp. -, 1976-1978 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Activities, undated (Box 62)
  - Arthur Capper Demonstration Project n.d., undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Capper Demonstration Project, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Capper Demonstration Project, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Capper Demonstration Project, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Arthur Capper Demonstration Project, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Capper Demonstration Project, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Problems with rats, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Housing Survey, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Housing Survey Report, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Capper Center - plans, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - The Housing Team - UPO NDP, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Arthur Capper Center, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Potomac Gardens Multi Service Center explained, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Potomac Gardens monthly reports, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - The Housing Team, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Arthur Capper Clinic, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Arthur Capper Center - Staff and programs, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Arthur Capper Center - Staff and programs, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Potomac Gardens monthly reports, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Potomac Gardens Inter-agency Committee, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Potomac Gardens Multi Service Center Annual Report, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Potomac Gardens Progress Report, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Activities, undated (Box 63)
  - Housing problems - monthly reports, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Capper - rent strike, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Potomac Gardens, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Summary of housing programs, 1970 ca. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Resident Councils, 1970 ca. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Kentucky Courts - dedication, 1970 ca. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Ellen Wilson Center - photo, 1970 ca. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Potomac Gardens - monthly reports, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Housing - monthly reports 197., undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Folder 10 does not exist. That number was skipped in the original finding aid.
  - Arthur Capper - poor conditions, article, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Capper - tenants, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Testimonies on Rent Control, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Testimonies, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Capitol East Housing Commission - participation, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Arthur Capper, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Arthur Capper Clinic closing, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Housing - Target Project Program, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Housing - Target Project Program, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Housing - Target Project Program, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    Folder 21 does not exist
  - Architect's plan for Arthur Capper Multi Service Center, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Activities, undated (Box 64)
  - Pamphlet - "Stand Up and Fight Book", 1976 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Capper Center - tribute, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - "Capper Chronicle" newsletter, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Capper Center - Advisory Board Bylaws, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Arthur Capper Center - newsletter, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Capper Center - Security plan, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Application for funds from DC Department of Housing, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Arthur Capper Center - Advisory Board Bylaws, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Housing - testimony for Block Grant, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Capitol East Neighborhood Housing Center, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Housing - statement, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Capitol East Neighborhood Housing Center, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing and Neighborhood Improvement, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Sample Housing Contracts - assistance program, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Housing Counselling Program - DC funding, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Neighborhood Profile, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Activities, undated (Box 65)
  - Volunteers - statement, n.d., undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Friendship House Volunteers - "What is a Settlement?" and "What Can a Volunteer Do?" - statements, pamphlets n.d., undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Volunteers and Board Members, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1940 ca. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1943 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Lists of Volunteers, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Junior League Program at Friendship House, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Call for Volunteers, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Applications from volunteers, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Applications from volunteers, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Applications from volunteers, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - The volunteers' program, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Volunteer forms, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Obituary - Virginia Corman, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Volunteers, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Volunteers, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Obituary - Mrs. Milton King, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Volunteers - monthly reports, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Volunteers - Memorabilia, 1970 ca. (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Volunteers - monthly reports, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Memorial Service - Mabel Taylor, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Brochure 197., undated (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - VISTA Volunteers, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    [VISTA also box 99]
  - Activities, undated (Box 66)
  - Friends of Friendship House, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Friendship House, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Friends of Friendship House, 1948 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Financial statement, 1949-1956 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Fund raising event - Silver Tea, 1953. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Event - Capitol Hill Secretary's Dinner, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Event - Capitol Hill Secretary's Dinner, 1956-1957 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1958 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Event - Capitol Hill Secretary's Dinner, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Fundraising, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Fundraising, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1965-1966 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1967-1968 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Letter of Appeal, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Contributions, members, work on Market Day, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Friends of Friendship House:, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Appeal, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Friends of Friendship House: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - Friends of Friendship House: General material, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - Activities, undated (Box 67)
  - Circle on the Hill fact sheet, 1950 ca. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Circle on the Hill Auction, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Circle (Congressional wives) - Auction, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Circle benefit, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Circle benefit concert, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Circle and Circle on the Hill - Organization and Explanation, 1960 ca. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1960 ca. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit auction, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Circle, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Circle, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Circle on the Hill, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Circle on the Hill - Urban program article, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Congressional Circle - Soup luncheon, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Circle on the Hill - correspondence, notices, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Circle, Circle on the Hill benefits, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Circle on the Hill - benefit, 10/1963 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Circle on the Hill - correspondence, notices, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Circle - Mrs. Bolling's re-election, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Circle on the Hill - Mrs. Boggs chairman of Market Day '64, undated (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit dance, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Congressional Circle, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit for Friendship House, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit garden party, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Circle on the Hill - correspondence, notes, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Circle on the Hill -, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Congressional Circle, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit dinner dance, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Congressional Circle - benefit fashion show, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Circle on the Hill, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Circle on the Hill - correspondence, Market Day, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Circle on the Hill, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Circle on the Hill - contributions to Beautification, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Circle on the Hill - Christmas party, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Circle on the Hill - Correspondence 196., undated (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Congressional circle, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Congressional Circle - Charity Dance, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Activities, undated (Box 68)
  - Congressional Circle, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Circle - list of members, 1968-1969 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Circle on the Hill, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Circle on the Hill - Nina Simone Concert, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Circle on the Hill - Market Day, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Circle on the Hill - brochure on the organization, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - House tours, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - House tours, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - House tours, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Articles on the House Tours, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - House Tours - Mrs. Eisenhower requested to attend and reply, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    This folder contains photographs, (original removed)
  - House Tours - Mrs. Eisenhower requested to attend and reply, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    This folder contains photographs (original removed)
  - Capitol Hill tours, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - House Tours - plans, photos, articles, participants, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - House Tours - plans, photos, articles, participants, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - House Tours - plans, photos, articles, participants, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - House Tours - plans, photos, articles, participants, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - House Tours - plans, photos, articles, participants, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - House Tours - plans, photos, articles, participants, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - House Tours - plans, photos, articles, participants, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Capitol Hill Tours - plans, articles, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Capitol Hill Tours - plans, articles, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - House Tours, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - House Tours, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - House Tour, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - House Tour "Rambling Through Capitol Hill" brochure, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Market Day - photos, slides, negatives, 1970 ca. (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Market Day - photos, slides, negatives, 1970 ca. (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Market Day - photos, slides, negatives, 1970 ca. (Box 68, Folder 34)